We have a live feed.
Yes, sir.
And now, please give us a few last words, please.
Coming in, five seconds.
Four, three.
Well, today, 10 May.
10 May, 10 May.
10 May, which is, you know, 365 days.
I don't know what it is, but it's a special day.
It's no exaggeration. It's no exaggeration.
It's a big deal in Japan.
Probably where I'm from.
Mitaka City, Tokyo, is on parade after parade right now.
All the citizens of Mitaka are already here.
About 190,000 people all together.
Wow.
Cherry blossoms.
I think they're like...
But, you know, it's already late at night.
It's been going on during the day, and now it's nighttime, and everyone's already grown up.
Like, cheers.
I'm sure they're like, ‘Wow!
Welcome.
Good evening.
What a nice place to live.
This is the famous Miss Gaunt.
It was Miss Gaunt.
Yes, yes, yes.
Good evening.
Good evening. - Good evening.
Doctor, they're talking about the weak yen and the strong dollar these days.
That's right.
How's it going?
It's tough.
Morning.
Everything seems expensive.
It sure does.
Yes, it does.
It all seems expensive.
It's expensive, it's expensive, it's expensive.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, Master.
That's great.
You're good, Master.
Congratulations!
Isn't it like that every year?
Every year, when it's Ebitu's birthday...
There's a lot of stuff in the back.
The staff will make sure you don't miss it.
Please give this as a present today.
They say, ‘Please bring it out as a present today.
Let's have a look, shall we?
By the master himself.
Sorry.
There's the customary one.
The usual.
It's heavy.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
Look.
Oh, no.
It's heavy.
What the hell?
Wow.
This is...
Look, it's got TVK stamped on it.
Dumbbells with TVK stamped on them?
Yes, they are.
Here, take these.
Here's a set of weights, you know, to keep them from falling over.
I'm the one who buys them to hold them up so they don't fall over. They're really heavy, so be careful with these.
Be careful not to drop it. It's a bit heavy, isn't it?
It's a little tough, isn't it?
I'll take it with me.
Oh, teacher, Fur! What's that? You must be strong.
It's heavy. It's heavy.
Fur! I can't!
I can't do it.
It's pretty heavy.
It's a little bit no good.
I'll just put it back in its proper place.
You've done well, Master.
I'm impressed.
I'm stronger than I thought.
That's what I'm talking about.
Well, by the way, it's all right if you want a present or something, but you were very popular, weren't you, Master? You're surprisingly strong. I'm impressed.
By the way, it's okay to give gifts and stuff like that,
It's something you do out of courtesy,
It's not something we force you to do.
It's fine.
That's what I'm saying,
Master,
People born on 10 May,
I knew it,
All over Japan, all over the world,
There are people all over the world.
Including me, they're called May 10th.
It's a group I created, called May 10th.
May 10
By the way, for example...
In the field of entertainment, first of all, there's Ayako Fuji.
It's 10 May, 1961. Also, Mirai Shida.
She was born on 10 May. Also, Tomo Tetsuwan no Tomo. The guitarist.
That was in 1970. Also, you're the football player, Takeda-san. Choichiro-san is the narrator of Gundam.
Space Century.
I see. Amazing.
And Seed Vicious from the band Sex Pistols.
And Bono, the singer of the band U2.
Mr U2.
He's also on 10 May.
Since I started this job, I've had a lot of guests.
Surprisingly, I haven't had anyone with me on the exact same birthday as me.
The only one I've had in the last few years is Yanagi-chan, who is in her X-girls' generation.
10 May.
And by the way, these are actual people...
You know...
There are a lot of people with the 10th of May in fictional or even anime.
First of all, there's Rengoku from Oni no Hane no Kaede.
Mr. Rengoku.
May 10th.
The same day?
Yes, that's right.
And Drakken from Tokyo Revengers.
He's also 10 May.
And Gori from Slam Dunk.
10 May.
And Twice from Hiroaka.
You're with Twice?
How nice.
Mubai Gawaru.
He's a very nice guy.
On a more serious note, do you know Hitchdriss from Shingeki no Kyojin?
Who's that?
You see?
She's a girl in the Military Police.
She's a bit... a bit scruffy.
Right up to the end.
You see...
A friend of a friend... a boy...
She told him not to join the Survey Corps.
There was a girl who was a bit scruffy.
Hitch.
She's also 10th May.
10th May.
That's a lot of people.
And so on.
Probably in a lot of places now.
Probably some kind of fire breathing thing.
I think they're doing it.
It's a star's birthday.
That's what it's like.
Well...
Is it okay like that?
I don't know...
We've already got a lot of visitors.
I'm sorry.
What was that?
What's this?
Devil's Charge.
It's a name...
Charge. Charge.
It's out.
Sirene.
This is all I had to charge, so congratulations to the master.
Thank you very much.
By the way, Sirene... you got it.
Well...
Congratulations on your 58th birthday, Master.
Fifty-eight?
That's right, in two years I'll be 60.
So it's your 60th birthday?
Then I'll wear a red chan-chan.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, let's do it.
It'll look good on you.
Let's do it.
Let's do it the other way around.
I'll decide if I'm going to do it.
So...
Mr. Shirinu from Mishima City!
Thank you very much.
Happy birthday, Master!
I'll eat cake instead.
So...
You were kind enough to celebrate Master's birthday before.
How many years ago was it, about four or five?
Three years ago.
That was just about then.
That's when the Corona disaster was in full swing.
You know, there was that thing where you weren't allowed to move between prefectures.
That's why Sherna couldn't come.
She said she'd like it to happen again.
Sounds fun.
That's great.
Lovely cake.
A bruise.
Looks delicious.
But the tampres from the iced dumpling buns...
It's a double shot.
Let's take a picture together.
With the dumpling buns?
Then he ate the dumpling bun.
He's a bit shy.
It's so good!
Sorry.
From me too.
I've got something for you, too.
A photo of the two of us.
We've taken a lot of pictures.
Let me give you a shoulder rub.
I'd be happy to give you a shoulder rub dressed like this, but you know how it is these days.
Master...
Hey, Ma.
What's up, Ma?
By the way...
Saga Miharu Minami Ward's Devil's Touch has it.
Thank you
Happy birthday, Master.
For the first time
I was allowed to draw an illustration of Master
I was allowed to illustrate Master for the first time in Marstardeville, and Master!
I like the Master in the Devil, but I love the Master who smiles and talks to me while drinking beer in a delicious way when I meet him at live houses and other places.
So I wish Master a year in which he can enjoy beer and ramen.
So, I guess it's like this.
I'm sure he looks like this.
He's got a smile on his face, and he's live, that's for sure.
He doesn't seem shy at all, he's just a little bit processed.
You're drinking beer too fast, aren't you?
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Well, that's enough of my corner for today.
May I?
Yes, yes.
We've got a lot of visitors.
Thank you so much.
I've been getting so many that I've had to stop chatting.
That's great.
You're so cool, Nakahikahiho!
Congratulations!
It's Arakan, isn't it?
What's arakan?
Around the year
ARAKAN KISETSU
ARAKENBO
ARAKAN REGISTER
No, it's not.
How's it going? Like...
I didn't notice.
I didn't realise how perfect it was.
It's like Alaska.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Yuhi from Zanar.
Happy birthday, Master!
Two more years and you'll be perfect.
Mayamaama is 30.
Mayama Mayama is perfect too?
It's written.
It says 30 for you, Mayama.
I couldn't say it out loud myself.
Ah...
It means you're reaching a milestone, too, Mayama.
It's coming soon.
So, M. Nagaoka, Master Hapiba.
Ah, then, it's Happy Birthday!
Congratulations, Hamamin-san!
Sorry, for everything.
Happy birthday, Mineral-san.
Hamamatsuno.
Yes, we've received many gifts.
99sik, you also received a lot. Thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, and among them, I received many comments of congratulations. 99sik also. Thank you very much.
I've also received many comments of congratulations from many of them.
No, no, no, there's nothing I can do. I'm not going to be able to celebrate anymore.
I have no face.
I'm not going to be embarrassed.
Oh, the power of the eye.
Oh, my eyes.
By the way, in the quotes section, just in case it's my birthday, I'm going to give you a quote from me today.
It's good, isn't it?
I've already said quite a few.
That's right, I've made a lot of quotes.
Don't chew on that!
What's the matter with you? Are you harassing me?
We're making a lot of money.
It's a big deal.
By the way, Hino and Sheep, they sent it to Adachi Ward, Tokyo.
Just so you know, genius master, regular Sapong brother, Ebitu part-time worker, and staff, goodbye, Devil.
Can I say a few words of wisdom this time? I'll start with a quote.
I've got nothing but pig bones! I'll live with the pig's bones and I'll die with the pig's bones.
When are you going to say it?
It's amazing.
I do remember saying this.
When?
When what?
I don't know, it's just... a quote from a foreigner.
Billy Joel, who played the piano and sang and sang.
I met a man whose real name was William Martin Joel, who played the piano and sang and sang and sang, and his real name was William Martin Joel, so...
People who speak foreign languages have middle names, don't they?
I thought it was cool.
I had just started working part-time at the time.
I was about to turn 30 in two years.
I said...
No, no, no... it was written there.
Where it says ‘before’.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Zadar's superiority really got me. I'm going to hit you with my fishing line.
Zal 6 and the moon are the mechanisms, right? You're involved, more or less.
And we're going to give each other middle names, and I'm going to give Mayamaama a middle name, MayamaAnimérica.
Great! And then my sister wrote a series of letters, and her name is Kamurasimesabami for her.
Shime-saba? She told me what I was, and I told her I was from the Bertonkotsu Age, and that's how much I like tonkotsu ramen.
The bone.
That's the bone.
So, you know, everyone is like...
Like shimeji-saba and anime.
We all love it, don't we?
We also love tonkotsu (pork knuckle).
He said that.
I see.
That's a good quote.
It's true.
He's doing it right.
It's really long.
Like an inn book.
With pig bones.
It's a bit like a narration.
Live with the pig's bones.
Let us die with the pig's bones.
Like a warlord.
That's impressive.
The Pork Bone Shogun.
Shogun Pork Bone.
That's actually how I feel.
Pork bone ramen.
Well, well, well.
That's why...
Well then...
Let's see...
Well...
If you have any more letters, etc.
We'd like you to send us more and more.
I'll go straight to four, yes?
Congratulations. Congratulations, Master.
Congratulations, Master.
Your shoulders are stiff.
The gold medalists were amazing!
It's like... at the core.
Yes, they were.
I've known Kenji Otsuki for a long time, of course.
I was a little overwhelmed.
He hasn't changed at all.
Is that so?
He used to have less hair.
But his face hasn't changed at all.
I was surprised to hear so many wonderful things about you.
I didn't think you were that close in age. I'm three months older.
Yes, one difference. One difference. About three months.
One is almost, but not quite.
Great, yes, yes, that's why I've been receiving some letters,
Well, this is..,
This is..,
Mr. Blue Star.
Oh.
Mr Hadano.
Thank you very much.
The other day, before going to Yokohama Stadium to support the Bay Stars, I visited the Broadcasting Library on Nihon Odori.
When I entered the exhibition area of popular spring programmes, the first thing that caught my eye was a panel of Master, Sewa Serapun Ebichu-chan and others!
Thank you.
The museum devils were arranged in such a way that they were the first to be seen.
I thought, ‘That's just like our hometown in Kanagawa!
There's a place called Nihon Odori right next to the broadcasting library.
That's where TVK is, too.
It's an exhibition of popular programmes from NHK and other broadcasters.
But from TVK, we were wondering what TV programme would best represent TVK.
I'm sure they thought of this, even the president.
‘The Devil in the House,’ they said.
So we're going to do it.
That's why we're doing it on Yakatai Devil.
So this time, the level is featured prominently.
I'm so happy to see it like this... just today... just today... just today... just today... just today... just today...
They've sent me the same photo again.
The man from the pond...
Your parents, too.
Let's drink again.
This time... when we met, we were already in a terrorist cell.
We've had a little more time.
From the beginning.
If you'd been here, we could've had a better conversation.
Thank you.
By the way, this is exactly what we're doing now.
We're doing a live broadcast, and a popular TV show called ‘Important’ is also doing a live broadcast.
It's amazing that they're all together in the same building.
I'm really surprised. It's amazing that a popular TV show called ‘Devil in the House’ is here together.
It's amazing.
It's amazing!
We're going to make our debut together with Wings of the Tiger.
We're making our debut as Asatora?
We're making our debut?
We're making our debut!
I'm so happy!
By the way, admission is free.
If you have time or inclination, please come and say hi, hahaha, hahaha, hahaha, hahaha, hahaha.
If you have time or inclination, please come and say hello.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Then we'll all be like a kind of comrades.
That's right.
Right.
That's how it is.
And so...
Now, here it is, isn't it?
The photo of the dumpling buns was taken by a vendor...
You don't even know if it's a photo of dumplings.
First of all, I went to the famous Meissen shop.
I went to the main shop.
The main shop?
It's in Aoyama Omotesando.
The main shop's over there?
Yes, go there.
But still...
We sat at the counter.
They were already serving it right in front of me.
I could see him doing it.
Like a pork cutlet chef.
But I was really confused.
But the minced pork cutlet, limited to 30 servings, was still left.
So I went for that, and changed the tonjiru to tonjiru for 140 yen more.
No, no, no, no.
It was delicious.
What are you talking about?
It was a reward.
A reward?
Assuming you enjoyed the gig.
Well, we did our best.
I want to eat. What do you want to eat?
Pork cutlets.
Let's go.
That's it, isn't it?
Sandwiches?
It's famous, isn't it?
Delicious.
You've got it, haven't you?
You're so friendly with each other.
Just when you've had your fill, you come along and say...
What do you want to eat?
I want a crepe.
Is it around Gerapiquet?
This was in Omotesando Hills.
I'm so excited.
Are you okay on Omotesando?
It's more like a backstreet.
That's why I was so nervous. Alert... could it be Urasando?
I don't know where Urasando is.
I wonder where it is.
I was nervous going in.
I ate there.
Sugar crepes again!
and lemonade!
How stylish!
There's one around here, too?
Yes, there's one around here, too.
I thought I was full.
But it was fine.
I'm hungry.
A delicious holiday.
From that pork cutlet.
I was happy.
It's a reward.
Aisen's main shop...
It was so crowded.
I knew it...
I usually only eat ramen and soba.
I usually eat only ramen and soba... but with that mobile phone I unconsciously eat ramen and soba.
I'm always eating ramen and soba without even realising it.
But sometimes I look at the photos...
It's mostly ramen and soba.
It's like, ‘Did I ever eat this?
You can see the location of the restaurant.
With data.
Like, ‘Oh, there it is.
It's unconscious.
I'm a little curious about the pork cutlets.
You should definitely try it.
It's really fresh and crispy.
It's a real starby.
100,000 yen sauce is really good, and, um, more rice and rice cabbage? You can have another serving of rice and rice cabbage? Free! Free refills!
Oh, man!
I wanted a second helping.
I wanted another one, but why so hard?
I couldn't get past the waiter.
I couldn't say.
You're right.
But this is wonderful.
It's delicious.
I bet the pickles are good, too.
It was very good.
Wow!
It's good.
Well...
That's why, lately, I've been unconsciously saying ramen and soba whenever I leave it alone, so I thought I had to do something different.
So when Rei-chan Takagi from Kuroi came as a guest, she said she was going to eat Coco Ijika Curry's noodles, and since it's close by, I went there the first time, thinking it was a scary thing to see, and telling her not to lick my boots
I went there for the first time, and there was nothing I could do.
I've been there three or four times, but recently it's become a habit, I can go there now. - You can't really tell how spicy it is from the picture, but it's a Leni Curry.
Chef's food.
Seafood curry topped with two shots of natto.
This is just like that, but...
It's spicy anyway.
Normally, I'd say it's not spicy.
Amateurs like me can't just stand there and eat it.
I like this.
Squid.
It's got squid in it, too.
I love it!
Hey, what the heck, this is bad, isn't it?
I used about 4 cups in total.
If you don't do that, it's impossible for an amateur.
It's impossible for an amateur.
Amazing.
Ask the Fukurinzuke Corps to support us.
They're coming.
They've done a wonderful job.
Gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually...
Gradually, gradually, gradually, gradually...
Yes, it's going well. - Wow, it's painful. - What's that? What's that? Water.
No, the water in Hokoichi is definitely not the same as normal water.
It's spicy.
What? Is that so?
No, but I'm sure it is.
I don't have any scientific proof, but...
Wow, but you finished it.
That's why I'm getting into the habit of fighting so hard.
That's true.
So I usually just eat dinner, smoke a cigarette and go back to work.
Smoke again, eat, smoke again, work.
It's very squeezy.
I don't want to be like that anymore.
I don't want to do that anymore.
I'm looking for stimulation.
I really need to get into this Leni curry.
It's not very good.
First bite.
I thought, ‘Here it is again.
I've had it a couple of times now.
Oh, my God.